コンクリートの作り方を 覚えさせられた彼は 父親を殴り殺して 飛び出すまでの間
Formidable Enemy x And x Clear Objective
男手ひとつで彼を育てた父親は 寡黙だった
What's happening?
仕事を終えて部屋に戻ると
Where is the Supreme Leader?
２段ベッドの上にいる ジャイロに
It won't stop following us.
声をかけることは ほとんどなかった
That's annoying. It's the enemy's power.
ジャイロが７歳まで
I believe it won't disappear until we've damaged
ろくに言葉を話せなかったのは そのためだ
the enemy's physical body.
ジャイロは　仕事から戻ると 共同便所に行く時以外
Ah, how interesting. I shall test it.
ベッドから降りることを 許されていなかった 回数も一日２回
Incredible, that's my...
夜中に尿意を催し どうしても我慢できない時は
I understand. My power was not meant for me.
あらかじめ用意してある 空の酒瓶に用を足した
It was meant to be used by the King!
無口な父親が唯一
This does not make sense.
彼に事あるごとに 説いた教えだった ジャイロは　幼さ故の失敗を 重ねながらも この教えを 大切に守ろうとした オモチャの一つも買い与えられ なかった彼にとって
If you knew this power resulted
from an enemy's attack, that means either you saw it used, or it was used on you.
この言葉が 父親からもらった宝物だった
Which was it?
少年の小さな宇宙では 父親は神に等しかった
I was hit by an attack.
何より　どんなに ぞんざいな扱いを受けても 彼は父親を慕っていたし
I cannot see it following you now.
父親から必要とされていると 信じていた
So why does the enemy still live?
信じる根拠は　２つあった ジャイロが５歳くらいの時 高熱で死にかけたことがあった
How did you free yourself
from the enemy's power? Answer me.
徹夜でタオルを 替え続けてくれた
We made an agreement.
そして　もう一つ 自分は今まで
In exchange for releasing me from his power, I agreed to spare his comrade.
一度たりとも父親から 出て行けと言われたことがない この２つが 少年のひそかな誇りだった
Then, after he released you, you had the opportunity to finish
him off along with his comrade. Why did you not do so?
バカ！ 「出て行け」って言われねえのはな オメェが金づるだからだよ！
Honestly, I'm not sure.
心の奥底に　その可能性を 押し込めていた彼は 無神経に　そこをこじ開けた
I believe I felt that, if I had,
I would have lost in some way.
ひと回り以上　年上の青年に キレた 大事な秘密を 軽々と話してしまった後悔と
I felt that breaking a promise, even a promise to an enemy, would be equivalent to conceding defeat. Impossible!
自分への怒り
You're saying that your personal emotions
誇りを傷つけられた憎しみが 一気に噴出し
were the reason you spared the lives
of those who oppose the King?
青年に襲いかかった 普段から小ばかにしていた 弱気な少年の
I'm prepared to accept any punishment...
突然の造反に怒り狂った青年は
I have no excuses to offer.
彼を袋だたきにした後も 腹の虫が治まらなかった 少年の顔を 足で踏みつけたまま
I only ordered that you not lie to me.
唾とともに とどめのセリフを吐き捨てた オメェが熱出した時に 看病してたのは
I have no reason to punish
those who speak the truth.
隣のジジイだよ！
Pouf.
オメェの親父は　その時も
Yes! Youpi.
自分の部屋で 飲んだくれてただけだ。
Yes!
オメェは　うなされてて 知らねえだろうがよ
We have all obtained rather inconvenient bodies.
そのジジイと　オメェの親父は 夜中に大ゲンカしてんだ。
Our bodies and souls have been linked...
「自分の子供が死んだら どうする気だ」ってな。 その時　オメェの親父が 何て言ったか教えてやるよ。
It is no longer possible for the three of
us to hide anything from one another!
((別に… 死んだら死んだで構わねえよ))
Your Majesty! Your Majesty... Let us go.
ジャイロは 信じられないものを見た
Your Majesty... Was that meant as a final warning
確かに自分と目が合いながら
Nevertheless!
全く関心を示さず 通り過ぎて行く父親
Even if it means I am executed for my crime...
ジャイロは その時　全てを理解した
I do this for the King!
宇宙は　俺に興味がない
Where is she? Find her! Hurry up and find her! For the sake of our species! Where is she?
父親にとって 俺は死んでもいいし
Find her!
生きててもいい存在だった
She is not necessary!
つまり　どうでもよかった
Find her, quickly! I do this for the King. Is she over there?
生きていれば金が入るし
Wait! Not there! No! That way! Hey!
死ねば　少し部屋が広くなる それだけだ 「ヒトに迷惑を掛けるな」とは
When you're split up, you can't hurt me.
結局　しわ寄せが 父親自身に行くから
You're ignoring me? Wait up! You can't remove APR without defeating me!
あの言葉は 息子のためなどではなく
Youpi, the enemy suddenly appeared before me.
１００％　父親自身のためのもの
Does the enemy who attached this
「ヒト」は　父親のこと
also have the ability to teleport? That's someone else...
否
There's one who can make himself
and those around him invisible.
「ヒト」とは　人間だ
He looks like a chameleon.
俺は　人間じゃなかったんだ
So you spared not only humans,
but a traitor, as well?
少年は しばらくして立ち上がり
I'm willing to accept any punishment. Your Majesty!
そのまま　近くにあったハンマーを 手に取った
Until we've defeated them, please... I do not care. It is irrelevant.
ジャイロは　９年後 ＮＧＬを設立する
that Chimera Ants must overcome to evolve.
さらに９年後　それは国家となり 彼は王となる ジャイロは　全世界に 悪意をばらまきたかった
Youpi... We must accept your emotional instability, as well as the traitor's betrayal, as we move forward.
飲む麻薬　ディーディーは
Humans are a sacrifice meant to help
us attain the next level of evolution.
そのための まだ　ほんの手始めであった
The perfect sacrifice.
ユンジュ！ コルトの奴に 随分あっさりと引き渡したわね。
The King's opinion had completely
reversed following the explosion. Was it due to the impact?
どの道　餌は女王様行きだ。
No. This was the King, as well.
俺は狩りを楽しめればいい。
If the enemy can become invisible, I can find him by making contact.
ジャイロか
I need to split myself
クソ！ 黙って食っときゃよかったぜ いいか！　この工場は俺が頂く！
into the smallest clones
that can still retain sight, and expand the search!
今日から　ここが俺の城だ！
Bastard...
ウッハッハッハ…！
He turned back just like that... Who is he after? Is he looking for the traitor, Meleoron?
ギャッハハハハ…！
That's bad, then!
これ　最高！
I can't think of any way to defeat the
King without Meleoron's ability...
ギャハハハ　アッハハ！
I must protect Meleoron at any cost!
アハハハ…！　アハハハ…！ アハハハ…！
Pouf divided his clones to the point where
they're too small for me to see.
ヤバい あの生き物　ヤバ過ぎる
Unlike his main body, his clones have to be
見て！
at full size for me to see them.
一体…。
They must know we've realized
that the chameleon is a traitor.
一体　ここで何が起こってるんだ？
In other words, they believe that I've
returned to dispose of the traitor.
何？　さらに兵の死骸が？
Assuming the chameleon is concealing
himself and the others as they flee, and that the woman is among them, if I get close, they will protect the
chameleon and abandon her!
ああ　見つかったのは ザザンとこの３匹だ。
Because they believe the
chameleon is my target.
完全に信号が途絶えて 今も戻らない。
They must have never imagined that I'd return
銃を持つ奴らは ユンジュ隊が制圧した。
to kill the woman that Pitou was
trying so desperately to heal.
その他にも　俺達に抵抗する 人間達がいるということか？ まぁ　そういうことだろうな。
If they believe I've returned to rescue
the woman, it's even better!
だが　見つかった死骸は 銃とは違う何かで 射抜かれてたそうだ。
They may even offer to hand her
over to me with conditions.
俺が知るかよ。 奴らが持つ 未知の武器ってことだろ。
He must be after Meleoron.
兵の死骸は　どこだ？ ペギーが上で調べてる。
Since, from their perspective, he's a traitor. Hold on.
こいつは銃で撃たれている。 体内に弾が残っていたから 間違いないが
Let's make sure.
ただでさえ　下級兵の信号は 単純で要領を得んのだが 人間が何かを撃つまねをしたら
The door leading underground?
何も飛んで来なかったのに 頭を破壊されて倒れたというんだ。
So that's it... They realized that I know they
can become invisible, and decided to give me two options.
兵の中には物を見るだけでなく 感じる奴もいるだろ。 その通り　そういうタイプの兵は
The chameleon either ran inside
or fled somewhere else.
確かに何かが発射されたのを 感じている。
Their plan is to split up my clones
further, to weaken me.
我々の持たざる能力を 持っている。
No! Over there! Over there!
思ったより手ごわいぞ　人間は。
Over there! Over there! Over there!
それを受け継いでいる俺達にも 使えるってことだ
What?
奴らは手段を選ばず 彼女を殺しに来るぞ。
They're giving me two options.
ん？ 分かってねえのは　お前だ！
But they're to pursue the traitor or the woman?
だったら　俺達も 手段を選ばず 女王様を守ればいいだけの話だ。
Then they want to know which is my target?
違うか？ うむ…　まぁ確かに　その通りだ。
Do I split up my clones, to hide my objective?
そうさ　必ず守る
Or do I send the majority of them after
the chameleon, to fool them?
レイナは　俺が守る。 「レイナ」？
Even if the shutter is closed, I can slip through it if my clones are particle-sized.
誰だ？　レイナって。
No, I don't have time for that!
俺が？　俺は何も言ってないぞ。
I'll go after
お前の空耳だろ。
the woman!
そんなことより　問題は
So she's his target?
人間が下級兵クラスを 殺傷できる武器を
I only have to kill the woman
何種類も持っているということだ。
and hide her body from the
King for a short time.
うむ…　どうする？ 奪って使えばいい。
My clone can manage that! I only need a minute or two!
だが　人間は そんなこと分からないだろう。
He's...
相当　脅威に感じるはずだ。 なるほど。
incredibly fast!
私より　お前のほうが 参謀に向いているわい。
Then she's your target? I'm up for a game of tag.
「レイナ」？
Judging by how quickly he reacted, it would be hard to catch him,
even at full strength.
ダメね メッセージを受け取ってないわ。
If I don't hurry, the King will arrive. What do I do?
連絡をとり合ったハンター達は 全滅したってことよ。
Out of options, Pouf arrived at a diabolical solution.
そうか…。
I know!
戻ろう！ 俺達だけで手に負えるレベルの 生き物じゃ　ない。
The greatest magic of all...
一度　ＮＧＬを出て 全世界に　このことを発表し
He split himself up? But he won't be big enough to take her away!
駆除隊を結成する。 何でもいいから 早く　ここから逃げようぜ！
Is he going to attack me first?
このままじゃ　みんな…。
Your plan is going to backfire...
あっ？
Your plans have already been thwarted!
で…　で…
What is the point in adding
to your transgressions?
出た!! うわ!!
If it is fear of retribution driving
you to flee, you needn't worry.
逃げろ！　仲間が集まって来るぞ！
Don't make me laugh! You think I'll believe that?
おいおい
You'll probably tie me to a tree,
and turn me into a soldier!
生かして女王様へ献上するんだべ。
The King?
ひ…　人の顔。 何なのよ　こいつ！
That's right... Keep running.
撃て！　撃ってくれ!!
Take her far from the King first!
あっ！ 七色の矢の中で
I don't know the reason, but this girl is important to the King.
最速の「橙の矢」を いとも簡単に…
For Gon... For the sake of our mission...
何だ　はっきり見えるでねえか。
I can't let the enemy have her! That's right...
下級兵っこどもは　こんなもんも 見ることできねえんだべか。
The person chasing us sounded like one of the people with the Supreme Leader...
お前さんの体を覆っている 生命力そのものともいえる エネルギーが　その武器の源だな。
Does that mean the King is the Supreme Leader? Then who is this person?
女王様にとって 最上級の栄養食になりそうだべ。 フフフ…。
Who are the people he was with? Your twisted sense of justice
will never help the people!
あっ！ あぁ！ うわ！
First, I cast a spell on the woman. I use magic words to make her suspicious...
バルダ!! あ。
The King and I seek open dialogue. Now, release her at once!
あ…。
Bastard... That's just a bunch of baloney.
あっ　あ　しまった！
What is he up to? Let me go...
また反射的に食っちまっただ！
Please put me down! Something's wrong with you!
あ　また　ザザン様に 怒られちまうだな。
You're all tingly! What are you talking about, fool?
貴様！
I'm trying to save you!
ちょっ　ちょっと　たんま！
You trust that insect more than you trust me? Insect?
手が　ふさがっちまっただよ！
What are you talking about?!
うおっ！
Let go! Let me go! That's right... She can't see!
食らえ！
That'll make it hard to explain.
ザザン様！
It didn't take long for the poison to kick in.
持ってるものを 放せばいいでしょ？ あっ　本当だ。
If the woman you're carrying resists,
your speed will also fall...
いい獲物が手に入ったからね。 こいつは普通の人間の
What's going on? He wasn't aiming for me... He was aiming for the woman.
１０００人分にも値する 栄養がありそうね。
He was trying to kill her!
あっ　ザザン様！ ありがたき　お言葉 身に余る光栄でありますべ！
If she distracts him with her resistance, allowing me to kill her, even better! Komugi-san!
ほら　獲物！ あぁ　そうでした！
The enemies consider you a valuable hostage.
私じゃ助けられない 応援を呼ばなきゃ
Keep struggling! Keep fighting back! I'll save you soon!
すぐに食べられてしまう わけじゃ　ない！
She was knocked out, so that's impossible.
一刻も早く 国境へ戻らなきゃ！
If you enter this ring, I'll kill you.
キッヒヒヒ…。
If I burn those cells, they die.
おもしれぇ。
Are you having difficulty?
狩りって　おもしれぇ。
Your first priority should be regaining
your memories, Meruem-sama.
かなり危険だが…。 一緒に来るか？ もちろん。 俺達もプロだぜ。
They belong to me? You will rule these dumb, inferior creatures, and stand atop the food chain. That is your glorious destiny!
通訳さん 悪いが先を急ぐんでな。
As willed by the heavens!
２人は国境へ戻って 他の連中と合流し
Something isn't right...
協会へ連絡してくれ　危険生物だ。 了解！ 気をつけてね　カイト。
There's still something else...
ああ。 ついて来れなきゃ　置いてくぞ。
Something else I've forgotten.
こっちのセリフだね。 準備ＯＫ！
What are you saying? Nothing could be more important
than ruling over all life forms...
行くぞ。
Perhaps the explosion has left me confused.
ん？
It has been completely destroyed...
これ　薬きょうじゃん。
I suppose I should look at what's left.
機械の類いは　一切 持ち込めないはずだよね。 裏の支配者達は ドラッグだけじゃなく 銃も 密造していたってことさ。
Yes, you may find something that will
help you regain your memories...
だけど　この現状は…。
This is bad!
人間の仕業ではない。 恐らく　キメラアントだ。
That could be it... The Gungi board and pieces!
もしも　そのキメラアント達が 銃を扱えたとしたら…。
They may be the key to awakening his memory! I must dispose of them!
想像したくないが 裏の支配者達も　すでに 女王の餌に なっているかもしれない。
He gave up?
思いつく限り　最悪の組み合わせ
Over there.
未曽有のバイオハザードになる。
Let's go.